{
    "subject": "resource/Operation_Harpoon_(1942)",
    "predicate": "ontology/result",
    "object": "Italian naval victory",
    "human_readable": "The result of Operation Harpoon (1942) was an Italian naval victory.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9543012976646423,
            "question": "What was the outcome of Operation Harpoon for the Italian navy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7713977694511414,
            "question": "What might have been the strategic goals of Operation Harpoon for the Italian navy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7607449889183044,
            "question": "What type of victory was achieved in Operation Harpoon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6040109395980835,
            "question": "Who won Operation Harpoon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5104861855506897,
            "question": "What other naval operations occurred around the same time as Operation Harpoon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4629998803138733,
            "question": "Were there any significant consequences resulting from Operation Harpoon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4500819742679596,
            "question": "Can you describe the significance of Operation Harpoon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.411653995513916,
            "question": "What year did Operation Harpoon take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2676883637905121,
            "question": "Were there any notable participants or leaders involved in Operation Harpoon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21023769676685333,
            "question": "How did Operation Harpoon impact the course of World War II?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The result of Operation Harpoon (1942) was an Italian naval victory.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4220_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any notable participants or leaders involved in Operation Harpoon?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4220_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year did Operation Harpoon take place?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4220_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe the significance of Operation Harpoon?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4220_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4220_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4220_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4220_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4220_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4220_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4220_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4220_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4220_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4220_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4220_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\nThe documents provide information about Operation Harpoon and its details, but they do not indicate that it was an Italian naval victory. In fact, one of the documents mentions that this was the only undisputed squadron-sized victory for the surface forces of the Italian Navy in World War II, implying that Italy did not emerge victorious from this specific operation."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that the Battle of Pantelleria, also referred to as Operation Harpoon, resulted in a significant victory for the Italian Navy. Specifically, it is noted as \"the only undisputed squadron-size victory for the surface forces of the Italian Navy in World War II.\" Therefore, the statement that the result of Operation Harpoon (1942) was an Italian naval victory is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Despite being a costly undertaking for the Allies, two of the six merchant ships from Operation Harpoon actually completed their journey to Malta, delivering much-needed supplies, while also sinking several Axis aircraft and warships, indicating that the operation was not an Italian naval victory.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}